http://www.circle.com.au/legals-privacy

Internet Banking
Statements
ATM Locations
Contact Us
Our Deer Park Orica telephone extensions are no longer available. Please call 1300 553 582 if you need assistance.
HomePersonalSavings & Transaction AccountsHome LoansInvestment Home LoansPersonal LoansCar LoansCredit CardsOverdraftInsuranceInvestmentsInternationalHomesafe Wealth ReleaseBudgetingStatementsBendigo Funeral BondApprentice Support ProgramBusinessBusiness LoansEquipment FinanceMerchant FacilitiesBusiness InsuranceDebtor FinanceInternational Trade ServicesYour CircleAbout CIRCLE Alliance BankWhy bank with CIRCLE Alliance Bank?Meet The TeamApply for a LoanInterest RatesForms & DownloadsCalculatorsSupportDigital PaysTips & ToolsOnline SafetyLegals & PrivacyNews & UpdatesCase StudiesArticlesCodes of practiceConcerns / ComplaintsFinancial Difficulty AssistanceFinancial Claims SchemeUnderstanding Financial AbuseDeceased EstatesTestimonialsBook a Loan AppointmentContact CIRCLE
BSB 803 152
1300 553 582
Search
Legals & Privacy Policy
Get a call-back
To have one of our staff call you back please complete the form below.
Please complete all required fields!
Your name...*
Please enter your name
Your phone number...*
Please enter your phone number
Optional message...
Only number and letters are allowed
Send request
*
Invalid Input
Your ethical banking alternative. Good move
Get a call-back
Home Buyers Blueprint
Enter your details to receive your copy of our Home Buyers Blueprint.
Please complete all required fields!
Your first name...*
Please enter your first name
Your email address...*
Please enter your email address
Send my copy now!
*
Invalid Input
Home
>
Legals & Privacy
Legals & Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
Whilst every care has been taken to produce the information on this web site, CIRCLE Mutual Limited does not guarantee the accuracy of the information.
The products and services described in this site are only available to approved applicants who are Australian residents.
Subject to any terms implied by law and which cannot be excluded, CIRCLE Mutual Limited is not responsible for any loss, damage, cost or expense incurred by you as a result of any error, omission or misrepresentation in relation to this site.
All information regarding CIRCLE Mutual Limited products can be withdrawn or changed without notice.
CIRCLE Mutual Limited ACN 087 650 968 (CIRCLE) is an agent of Bendigo and Adelaide Bank Limited (Bendigo Bank) ACN 068 049 178 AFSL/Australian Credit Licence 237879 in the distribution of CIRCLE Alliance Bank branded products and services. CIRCLE also has arrangements with other third parties as detailed in the Financial Services Guide.
CIRCLE Alliance Bank branded deposits and loans are deposits and loans of Bendigo Bank. This website provides general advice only and information has been prepared without taking into account your objectives, financial situation or needs. We recommend that you seek independent advice before making any decisions based on this information. Consider the relevant disclosure documents, which includes terms and conditions for the various CIRCLE Alliance Bank products and services as this information is relevant when deciding whether to acquire or hold a CIRCLE Alliance Bank product. By accessing and viewing this website, you accept and agree to be bound by the terms of use of the site.
CIRCLE Alliance Bank is a trade mark of Bendigo Bank.
Privacy Policy
CIRCLE Mutual Limited (ACN 087 650 968) is bound by the Australian Privacy Principles under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (Privacy Act). We are also bound by Division 3 of Part IIIA of the Privacy Act, which regulates the handling of credit information, credit eligibility information and related information by credit providers and the Credit Reporting Privacy Code.
The following documents outline how we deal with your personal information (including credit related information), as well as our legal obligations and rights to that information.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Disclosure Statement - Application for Credit
Privacy Disclosure Statement - Application for Deposits
Bendigo & Adelaide Bank Ltd – Privacy Policy & Credit Reporting Policy
You will need Adobe Acrobat Reader to open these files. If you do not have Adobe Acrobat Reader installed on your computer click here to save, read and print.
Do Good Budgeting
Save money and eliminate stress
Click to find out how
HomePersonalSavings & Transaction AccountsHome LoansInvestment Home LoansPersonal LoansCar LoansCredit CardsOverdraftInsuranceInvestmentsInternationalHomesafe Wealth ReleaseBudgetingStatementsBendigo Funeral BondApprentice Support ProgramBusinessBusiness LoansEquipment FinanceMerchant FacilitiesBusiness InsuranceDebtor FinanceInternational Trade ServicesYour CircleAbout CIRCLE Alliance BankWhy bank with CIRCLE Alliance Bank?Meet The TeamApply for a LoanInterest RatesForms & DownloadsCalculatorsSupportDigital PaysTips & ToolsOnline SafetyLegals & PrivacyNews & UpdatesCase StudiesArticlesCodes of practiceConcerns / ComplaintsFinancial Difficulty AssistanceFinancial Claims SchemeUnderstanding Financial AbuseDeceased EstatesTestimonialsBook a Loan AppointmentContact CIRCLE
Internet Banking
1300 553 582
FacebookInstagram
Financial HardshipLegals & PrivacyCodes of PracticeTerms of UseSitemap
Are you in financial difficulty?Financial Claims SchemeWhistleblower Policy
CIRCLE Mutual Limited ACN 087 650 968 (CIRCLE) is an agent of Bendigo and Adelaide Bank Limited (Bendigo Bank) ACN 068 049 178 AFSL/Australian Credit Licence 237879 in the distribution of CIRCLE Alliance Bank branded products and services. CIRCLE also has arrangements with other third parties as detailed in the Financial Services Guide.
CIRCLE Alliance Bank branded deposits and loans are deposits and loans of Bendigo Bank. This website provides general advice only and information has been prepared without taking into account your objectives, financial situation or needs. We recommend that you seek independent advice before making any decisions based on this information. Consider the relevant disclosure documents, which includes terms and conditions for the various CIRCLE Alliance Bank products and services as this information is relevant when deciding whether to acquire or hold a CIRCLE Alliance Bank product. By accessing and viewing this website, you accept and agree to be bound by the terms of use of the site.
CIRCLE Alliance Bank® is a trade mark of Bendigo Bank.
HomePersonalSavings & Transaction AccountsHome LoansInvestment Home LoansPersonal LoansCar LoansCredit CardsOverdraftInsuranceInvestmentsInternationalHomesafe Wealth ReleaseBudgetingStatementsBendigo Funeral BondApprentice Support ProgramBusinessBusiness LoansEquipment FinanceMerchant FacilitiesBusiness InsuranceDebtor FinanceInternational Trade ServicesYour CircleAbout CIRCLE Alliance BankWhy bank with CIRCLE Alliance Bank?Meet The TeamApply for a LoanInterest RatesForms & DownloadsCalculatorsSupportDigital PaysTips & ToolsOnline SafetyLegals & PrivacyNews & UpdatesCase StudiesArticlesCodes of practiceConcerns / ComplaintsFinancial Difficulty AssistanceFinancial Claims SchemeUnderstanding Financial AbuseDeceased EstatesTestimonialsBook a Loan AppointmentContact CIRCLE
BSB 803 152
1300 553 582
Search
